<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on</title><link>https://kouhoumed.com/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kouhoumed.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ChatSage: a multi-model chatbot application</title><link>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/chatsage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/chatsage/</guid><description>ChatSage GitHub repository
ChatSage is a multi-model chatbot application that allows users to interact with various language models including GPT-3, GPT-4, Claude, and custom models.
Features Support for multiple language models (GPT-3, GPT-4, Claude, LLaMA, and custom models) Web-based chat interface API endpoints for chat functionality Configurable settings for different environments Basic rate limiting Chat history management Installation Clone the repository:
git clone https://github.com/KouhouMed/chatsage.git cd chatsage Create a virtual environment and activate it:</description></item><item><title>Building a Real-Time Stock Market Data Pipeline with Apache Kafka and Cassandra</title><link>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/kafka-cassandra-rt-stock-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/kafka-cassandra-rt-stock-analysis/</guid><description>Building a Real-Time Stock Market Data Pipeline with Apache Kafka and Cassandra In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced financial markets, the ability to process and analyze real-time data is crucial. I recently embarked on a project to build a real-time stock market data pipeline using Apache Kafka and Cassandra. This project not only enhanced my understanding of distributed systems but also provided valuable insights into handling high-volume, time-sensitive data.
Project Overview The goal was to create a system that could:</description></item><item><title>Unveiling Market Insights: My CAPM Stock Analysis App</title><link>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/capm-analysis-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kouhoumed.com/blog/capm-analysis-app/</guid><description>Unveiling Market Insights: My CAPM Stock Analysis App In the ever-evolving world of finance, making informed investment decisions is crucial. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share a tool I&amp;rsquo;ve developed that brings the power of the Capital Asset Pricing Model (CAPM) to your fingertips: the CAPM Stock Analysis App.
What is CAPM? Before diving into the app, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly discuss CAPM. The Capital Asset Pricing Model is a fundamental concept in modern financial theory.</description></item></channel></rss>