<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Engineering on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/data-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Engineering on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/data-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering roadmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/data-engineering-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/data-engineering-roadmap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Data Engineering?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/data-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/data-engineering/</guid>
      <description>What is Data Engineering? Data Engineering is a relatively new field in data-related topics. When we are talking about data folks, we usually think about two types of responsibilities inside the team:&#xA;those who analyze the data those who prepare the data for analysis In the first category there are Data Analysts, Data Scientist, Data Visualization specialists, Product Analysts, etc.&#xA;In the second category there are more technical people: Data Engineers, BI developers, DevOps/DataOps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Real-Time Stock Market Data Pipeline with Apache Kafka and Cassandra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/kafka-cassandra-rt-stock-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/kafka-cassandra-rt-stock-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Building a Real-Time Stock Market Data Pipeline with Apache Kafka and Cassandra In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced financial markets, the ability to process and analyze real-time data is crucial. I recently embarked on a project to build a real-time stock market data pipeline using Apache Kafka and Cassandra. This project not only enhanced my understanding of distributed systems but also provided valuable insights into handling high-volume, time-sensitive data.&#xA;Project Overview The goal was to create a system that could:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
